http://www.langfords.co.uk/privacy

LANGFORDS SILVER SERVICES
HomeSERVICESSECTORSBESPOKE  STEP-BY-STEPCOMMISSIONSATLANTIDEINSPIRATION  CUTLERYBARWARETABLEWARETEA & COFFEECONTEMPORARYRetail SiteABOUT  ABOUT USBLOGCLEANING SILVEROUR BROCHURECONTACT
LANGFORDS SILVER SERVICES
HomeSERVICESSECTORSBESPOKE  STEP-BY-STEPCOMMISSIONSATLANTIDEINSPIRATION  CUTLERYBARWARETABLEWARETEA & COFFEECONTEMPORARYRetail SiteABOUT  ABOUT USBLOGCLEANING SILVEROUR BROCHURECONTACT
HomePrivacy Privacy
Privacy Policy NoticeThe policy: This privacy policy notice is for this website; www.langfords.co.uk and served by Langfords Silver Services Ltd, Vaults 8 & 10, London Silver Vaults, 53-64 Chancery Lane, London WC2A 1QS and governs the privacy of those who use it. The purpose of this policy is to explain to you how we control, process, handle and protect your personal information while browsing or using this website, including your rights under current laws and regulations. If you do not agree to the following policy you may wish to cease viewing / using this website.Policy key definitions:"I", "our", "us", or "we" refer to the business [Langfords Silver Services Ltd]."you", "the user" refer to the person(s) using this website.GDPR means General Data Protection Act.PECR means Privacy & Electronic Communications Regulation.ICO means Information Commissioner's Office.Cookies mean small files stored on a users computer or device.Processing of your personal dataUnder the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) we control and / or process any personal information about you electronically using the following lawful bases.We are exempt from registration in the ICO Data Protection Register because we are only processing personal data for the core business purposes.Your individual rightsUnder the GDPR your rights are as follows. You can read more about your rights in details here;the right to be informed;the right of access;the right to rectification;the right to erasure;the right to restrict processing;the right to data portability;the right to object; andthe right not to be subject to automated decision-making including profiling.You also have the right to complain to the ICO [www.ico.org.uk] if you feel there is a problem with the way we are handling your data.We handle subject access requests in accordance with the GDPR.Internet cookiesWe use cookies on this website to provide you with a better user experience. We do this by placing a small text file on your device / computer hard drive to track how you use the website, to record or log whether you have seen particular messages that we display, to keep you logged into the website where applicable, to display relevant adverts or content, referred you to a third party website.Some cookies are required to enjoy and use the full functionality of this website.We use a cookie control system which allows you to accept the use of cookies, and control which cookies are saved to your device / computer. Some cookies will be saved for specific time periods, where others may last indefinitely. Your web browser should provide you with the controls to manage and delete cookies from your device, please see your web browser options.Data security and protectionWe ensure the security of any personal information we hold by using secure data storage technologies and precise procedures in how we store, access and manage that information. Our methods meet the GDPR compliance requirement.Transparent Privacy ExplanationsWe have provided some further explanations about user privacy and the way we use this website to help promote a transparent and honest user privacy methodology.Email marketing messages & subscriptionUnder the GDPR we use the consent lawful basis for anyone subscribing to our newsletter or marketing mailing list. We only collect certain data about you, as detailed in the "Processing of your personal date" above. Any email marketing messages we send are done so through an EMS, email marketing service provider. An EMS is a third party service provider of software / applications that allows marketers to send out email marketing campaigns to a list of users.Email marketing messages that we send may contain tracking beacons / tracked clickable links or similar server technologies in order to track subscriber activity within email marketing messages. Where used, such marketing messages may record a range of data such as; times, dates, I.P addresses, opens, clicks, forwards, geographic and demographic data. Such data, within its limitations will show the activity each subscriber made for that email campaign.Any email marketing messages we send are in accordance with the GDPR and the PECR. We provide you with an easy method to withdraw your consent (unsubscribe) or manage your preferences / the information we hold about you at any time. See any marketing messages for instructions on how to unsubscribe or manage your preferences, you can also unsubscribe from all MailChimp lists, by following this link, otherwise contact the EMS provider.Our EMS provider is; MailChimp. We hold the following information about you within our EMS system;Email addressI.P addressSubscription time & dateName & Business Name
